那是家族企业  是在50年代
family business-- in the fifties.
嘉宝公司婴儿头像
我就像是湿巾业的"嘉宝婴儿"
I was kind of the gerber baby of moist towelettes.
-很厉害  皮尔斯  -是啊
- That's great, Pierce. - Yeah, yeah.
我有很多演出经验  出入片场
Oh, I've done a lot of acting. Workshops.
擅长肢体喜剧  滑稽舞蹈
I do physical comedy. Funny dances.
-模仿外国口音  -口音吗
- Foreign accents. - Accents?
随便说个国家
Name any country.
俄罗斯
Russia.
问题是  我能给短剧带来很多元素
Point being, there are many tools I can bring to the table
所以我认为剧本有点浪费我的才华
that I think the script may be wasting.
皮尔斯  你知道
Pierce, you know what I think
这个短剧哪里最棒吗
is really great about this show?
真正的明星是其传递的讯息
The only real star of it is the message.
是啊  那条讯息是杰夫·翁格吗
Right. Uh... is the message Jeff Winger?